http://www.bradthor.com/privacy-policy

BradThor.com Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that BradThor.com collects, and the ways in which BradThor.com uses that personal information.
BradThor.com may collect and use the following kinds of personal information: information about your use of this website, information about transactions carried out over this website, information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including Newsletter subscription through Benchmark email); and any other information that you send to BradThor.com.
BradThor.com may use your personal information to: administer this website, personalize the website for you, enable your access to and use of the website services, send to you products that you win in any contest, send you marketing communications.
In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, BradThor.com may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.
BradThor.com will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Personal information that you submit for publication on the website may be published on the internet and may be available around the world. You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information. BradThor.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.
You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.
BradThor.com links to other websites is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party. As you browse BradThor.comadvertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.  Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with BradThor.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.  You can visit this page to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or BradThor.com’s treatment of your personal information, please write by email to BradThorInformationTeam@gmail.com.
